kriskris.com 2013-06-06

# Privacy Policy | KrisKris.com

## Information that we collect

We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a contact or comment form. 

When filling out a form, you may be asked to enter your: name, website and e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy/ads/).

## What we use your information for

Any of the information we collect from you may be used to send you emails. 

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

The email service we use is called Aweber, and you can read their privacy policy [here](http://www.aweber.com/privacy.htm). At the bottom of each and every email sent to you, there is an unsubscribe link. If you click that link, you will remove yourself from the mailing list right away.

We will **never** share your email address with anyone.

## We do use cookies

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfer to your hard drive through your browser that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to compile data about site traffic and interaction so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future. 

We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## We do not disclose any information to outside parties

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our [Terms and Conditions](http://www.kriskris.com/terms-of-service/) section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

## Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on October 15, 2012.

## Contact Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

http://www.kriskris.com/

Bolstadarhlid 50  
Reykjavik, Gullbringusysla 105  
Iceland  
kristjan@kriskris.com  
+354-693-9246
